<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>docker on vesey.tech</title>
    <link>https://vesey.tech/tags/docker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in docker on vesey.tech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vesey.tech/tags/docker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>hddcheap</title>
      <link>https://vesey.tech/project/hddcheap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vesey.tech/project/hddcheap/</guid>
      <description>For homelabbers, locating cheap, shuckable hard drives is an occasional necessity. Amazon doesn&amp;rsquo;t expose an easy API to allow us to scrape drive data. Hddcheap gives you that live data in an easy-to-read grid format.
(I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed the camelcamelcamel images will not load if you are on a VPN - they are likely blocking known VPN IPs)
https://hddcheap.vesey.tech</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>versefind</title>
      <link>https://vesey.tech/project/versefind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vesey.tech/project/versefind/</guid>
      <description>Ever remember a snatch of lyrics from a song you know you have saved in your Spotify library?
Ever search for that brief phrase in Google but find only unrelated tracks?
That can be enough to drive a person crazy. I wrote a tool that lets you search through your library to find these earworms.
https://versefind.vesey.tech</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Lightroom as a hosted service?</title>
      <link>https://vesey.tech/post/lightroom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vesey.tech/post/lightroom/</guid>
      <description>Background As someone with a significant photo library, I often find myself wishing I could access old photos from the road.
Although remote file access softwares can let me dive through the basic directories, I often wish I could use my Adobe Lightroom Classic instance to sort and filter the photos so I can find the ones I am looking for without searching.
The problem is, however, most of the time I only have my phone on me - and Lightroom Classic is a Windows-only product.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
