<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>vesey.tech</title>
    <link>https://vesey.tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content on vesey.tech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vesey.tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>hddcheap</title>
      <link>https://vesey.tech/project/hddcheap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vesey.tech/project/hddcheap/</guid>
      <description>For homelabbers, locating cheap, shuckable hard drives is an occasional necessity. Amazon doesn&amp;rsquo;t expose an easy API to allow us to scrape drive data. Hddcheap gives you that live data in an easy-to-read grid format.
(I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed the camelcamelcamel images will not load if you are on a VPN - they are likely blocking known VPN IPs)
https://hddcheap.vesey.tech</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>versefind</title>
      <link>https://vesey.tech/project/versefind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vesey.tech/project/versefind/</guid>
      <description>Ever remember a snatch of lyrics from a song you know you have saved in your Spotify library?
Ever search for that brief phrase in Google but find only unrelated tracks?
That can be enough to drive a person crazy. I wrote a tool that lets you search through your library to find these earworms.
https://versefind.vesey.tech</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Lightroom as a hosted service?</title>
      <link>https://vesey.tech/post/lightroom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vesey.tech/post/lightroom/</guid>
      <description>Background As someone with a significant photo library, I often find myself wishing I could access old photos from the road.
Although remote file access softwares can let me dive through the basic directories, I often wish I could use my Adobe Lightroom Classic instance to sort and filter the photos so I can find the ones I am looking for without searching.
The problem is, however, most of the time I only have my phone on me - and Lightroom Classic is a Windows-only product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fisher</title>
      <link>https://vesey.tech/post/fisher/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vesey.tech/post/fisher/</guid>
      <description>Before I moved to California, I lived with some like-minded developers, and we managed to build a pretty useful environment for ourselves.
We ended up with two server racks totalling about 12 Us of equipment, with high-speed data links, high-density storage, and plenty of blinkenlights.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a diagram of what we built:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MarkBot adventures in ML and NLP</title>
      <link>https://vesey.tech/post/markbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vesey.tech/post/markbot/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always had a love for large datasets and the interesting things one can do with them, so when my roommate sent me his entire Google Hangouts and Facebook chat history, I knew what I had to do.
Enter MarkBot Goals In the past, I&amp;rsquo;ve implemented plenty of basic character-level RNNs and trained them on all sorts of text corpora, but this time I wanted to try something different, and utilize word embeddings to try and produce a more coherent Mark-based chatbot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>test post please ignore</title>
      <link>https://vesey.tech/post/testpostpleaseignore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vesey.tech/post/testpostpleaseignore/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m no good at writing sample / filler text
 ((MathJax))
(not MathJax)
$$MORE\ MathJax$$
$NO MathJax$
 Look, a list!
 foo bar baz  And here&amp;rsquo;s some code! 👍
$(function(){ $(&amp;#39;div&amp;#39;).html(&amp;#39;I am a div.&amp;#39;); }); &amp;hellip;Smaller and smaller and smaller</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://vesey.tech/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vesey.tech/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello. I&amp;rsquo;m a full-stack developer from Boston (now California).
I enjoy challenging problems, well-designed archtitecture, and containers!
Why don&amp;rsquo;t you take a look at my resume?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
